Sundaram Dwivedi

Software Engineer | Frontend

I am a Frontend Developer with experience in web development. Proficient in HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Tailwind, JavaScript, React and Redux. A quick learner with the ability to adapt to new technologies and work in a fast-paced environment.

Education

Amity University

Bachelor of Technology in Computer Science

2015 - 2019

Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- BOOTSTRAP
- TAILWIND
- JAVASRIPT
- REACT
- REDUX

sundaramdwivedi1996@gmail.com

8512882842

https://www.linkedin.com/in/sundaram -dwivedi-38a976140/

https://github.com/Sundaram218

Work Experience

Internship Virtual Analytics

May 2022 - September 2022

- Implemented Parallax Effect on company's website. https://virtualanalytics.ai/
- Worked on user interface of attendance management system.
 https://core.appymonk.com
- Worked on user interface of animal products website. Worked on dashboard and about us page. https://smilewithpets.com

Web Developer Virtual Analytics (Full Time)

October 2022 - November 2022

Projects

Shows Hub Project

 This project has been made to watch out the latest trending shows. React along with Material UI have been used to develop this project.

https://movie-series-trailer.netlify.app/

Query App

 This project is simply a quiz app that has customized topics. React along with Material UI have been used to develop this project.

https://quiz-10-app.netlify.app/

CERTIFICATION

https://www.freecodecamp.org/certification/fcc 827deb25-846e-4387-95d3-

3e6a0bbed791/javascript-algorithms-and-datastructures